hello everyone today we will discuss about ICICI
Lombard so this will be an interesting discussion
about how the price is moving so if we look
closely in the ICICI Lombards price action then we
can see it is clearly down by 34 from the top of
1650 uh so it's presently trading at 1092 levels
uh if we see how it performed since last five six
years so uh from the initial price of 690 from
the IPO price it went down went up by 139 and
then it has gone down by 34 percent at present
so if we look at the present level then it is
trading at the earlier levels which we could
see in covered or even before that so this
is trading at 3.5 years earlier levels so
this is a good thing about this that this gives
us opportunity to buy but then we need to be uh
clear or we need to have some investment plan when
we look at this stock because if we see there have
been even below levels like down levels uh below
this point also so like around 1850 uh this has
talk uh this stock had gone down so we need to be
prepared for this downfall also so what we can do
is we can invest in three uh Parts first we'll be
at the present level second will be between 1000
or 950 level and third will be between 900 to
850 level so uh we need to be prepared for this
uh this kind of drawdowns also and also I would
requests that don't invest big chunk uh big lump
sum amount have uh the investment plan in small
chunks if you look at from the fundamental point
of view then the market cap of this company is
at 54 000 levels and the PE is at 31.2 percent
but if we see a say this P compared to the
nifty 50 then we think it is at higher level
but when we look at the uh PE from the earlier
levels which it had gone so the median PE is at
47 whereas the present is 31 so this can also be
a good fundamental uh opportunity when we look at
this stock also if we look at the net profit then
it is trading at the highest net profit levels of
1700 whereas we are getting this stock at the
value of uh to 2020 level so uh this we should
keep in mind while investing also if we look
at the borrowings then uh we can set this as
an equitable borrowings so this is a good point
when we look at the shareholding patterns then
this is a negative point which we can say that
there has been decrease in the promoters holding
but overall we can say this is a good stock
to invest uh before investing would request
you to please check with your investment
advisor and do like share and subscribe to
my channel that will give me confidence and
I would be able to bring new stuff thank you